<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives - FIFA Online Mills</title>
	<atom:link href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/category/news/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 11:56:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Mikel Arteta responds to PSG and Arsenal exit link</title>
		<link>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/mikel-arteta-responds-to-psg-and-arsenal-exit-link/</link>
					<comments>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/mikel-arteta-responds-to-psg-and-arsenal-exit-link/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 11:56:44 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://fifa.online.mills.edu/?p=106</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mikel Arteta insists he is happy at Arsenal after being linked with a move to Paris Saint-Germain. The Spaniard guided the Gunners to a second-placed finish in the Premier League last season, while he won the FA Cup during his first season in charge. PSG, meanwhile, have been searching for a new manager following the</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/mikel-arteta-responds-to-psg-and-arsenal-exit-link/">Mikel Arteta responds to PSG and Arsenal exit link</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Mikel Arteta insists he is happy at Arsenal after being linked with a move to Paris Saint-Germain.</p>



<p>The Spaniard guided the Gunners to a second-placed finish in the Premier League last season, while he won the FA Cup during his first season in charge.</p>



<p>PSG, meanwhile, have been searching for a new manager following the sacking of Christophe Galtier earlier this month.</p>



<p>Former Barcelona and Spain head coach Luis Enrique is closing in on a move to the French capital to replace Galtier, but reports have claimed that PSG held talks with Arteta about the possibility of a move.</p>



<p>When asked about PSG’s interest, Arteta told Marca: ‘I can only say that I am happy at Arsenal.</p>



<p>‘I feel loved, valued by our owners, Stan and Josh [Kroenke], and I have a lot to do here at this club.</p>



<p>‘I am happy and tremendously grateful to be at Arsenal.’</p>



<p>Arsenal FC v Southampton FC &#8211; Premier League</p>



<p>Mikel Arteta insists Arsenal can win the Premier League title next season (Getty)<br>Asked if he would consider managing Barcelona or Real Madrid, Arteta replied: ‘Spain is my country. I have been out for many years and at some point it could be an option to return to the league and have other experiences.’</p>



<p>Arteta is also adamant that Arsenal will challenge for the Premier League title next season.</p>



<p>‘If not, I wouldn’t be sitting here. That’s our ambition,’ said the Arsenal manager.</p>



<p>‘We know the difficulty – it is the best League in the world and next season will be the most difficult League in the history of the Premier League. Why? Last year it was. I’ve been here for 22 years and I’ve never seen a competitive level like that.</p>



<p>‘So much quality, so much organization, so many resources, so many good coaches… and now Pochettino [at Chelsea] and Iraola [at Bournemouth] arrive.</p>



<p>‘The level is that and to win the Premier League you must be the best. That’s why we need to be reinforced.’</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/mikel-arteta-responds-to-psg-and-arsenal-exit-link/">Mikel Arteta responds to PSG and Arsenal exit link</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/mikel-arteta-responds-to-psg-and-arsenal-exit-link/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bayern Munich offer Todd Boehly major Mason Mount lifeline as Chelsea transfer tactic slammed</title>
		<link>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bayern-munich-offer-todd-boehly-major-mason-mount-lifeline-as-chelsea-transfer-tactic-slammed/</link>
					<comments>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bayern-munich-offer-todd-boehly-major-mason-mount-lifeline-as-chelsea-transfer-tactic-slammed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 11:55:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://fifa.online.mills.edu/?p=103</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Bayern Munich could revive Chelsea&#8217;s hopes of selling Mason Mount this summer after Manchester United reportedly walked away from negotiations. The 24-year-old midfielder faces an increasingly uncertain future at Stamford Bridge, with his contract set to expire at the end of next season. Unless the Blues manage to offload Mount this summer or in January</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bayern-munich-offer-todd-boehly-major-mason-mount-lifeline-as-chelsea-transfer-tactic-slammed/">Bayern Munich offer Todd Boehly major Mason Mount lifeline as Chelsea transfer tactic slammed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Bayern Munich could revive Chelsea&#8217;s hopes of selling Mason Mount this summer after Manchester United reportedly walked away from negotiations. The 24-year-old midfielder faces an increasingly uncertain future at Stamford Bridge, with his contract set to expire at the end of next season.</p>



<p>Unless the Blues manage to offload Mount this summer or in January then he&#8217;ll be free to leave the club in 12 months time. While Chelsea would rather charge a fee for the England international&#8217;s signature than seeing him leave for free, the club seem to be driving a hard bargain.</p>



<p>The west Londoners rejected a third bid from United worth £50million, including £5million worth of add-ons, a couple of days ago. Chelsea submitted a counter offer of £58million up front, in addition to a further £7million as add-ons, which Erik ten Hag&#8217;s side swiftly snubbed.</p>



<p>According to The Times, the Red Devils were unhappy with Chelsea&#8217;s proposal, adamant that they were being unfairly overcharged. As a result, they&#8217;ve reportedly ended their pursuit of Mount and Jason Cundy is far from impressed with his former club.</p>



<p>&#8220;I feel for Mason because he&#8217;s in a real situation where clearly he wants to join United, clearly he doesn&#8217;t see his future at Chelsea, Chelsea don&#8217;t see his future with them,&#8221; said the ex-Blues defender on talkSPORT, as quoted by the MEN.</p>



<p>&#8220;So now the Man United situation, he sat down, agreed terms, from what we understand, that bit&#8217;s done. It&#8217;s now for the two clubs to sort this out.</p>



<p>&#8220;He&#8217;s got a year left at Chelsea, doesn&#8217;t want to sign. This deal has got to be done in the next 10 days it feels like. What Man United have offered doesn&#8217;t reach Chelsea&#8217;s valuation of him even though he&#8217;s got a year left on his contract.</p>



<p>READ MORE:Chelsea news and transfers LIVE: Mason Mount twist, Moises Caicedo concern, Man Utd plan</p>



<p>Promoted Stories<br>&#8220;We are talking single-figure million pounds now, these are not big numbers in the grand scheme of things. There&#8217;s a common ground between what the two parties can decide. Meet in the middle, get it done, for the best of everyone.&#8221;</p>



<p>While United may be out of the race now, Bayern Munich could offer Chelsea a lifeline. According to The Guardian, the Bundesliga champions are stepping up their interest in Mount following the Red Devils&#8217; withdrawal from talks.</p>



<p>The report states that the Blues may be inclined to accept a lower fee from Bayern, but it remains to be seen whether the midfielder is open to leaving the Premier League.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bayern-munich-offer-todd-boehly-major-mason-mount-lifeline-as-chelsea-transfer-tactic-slammed/">Bayern Munich offer Todd Boehly major Mason Mount lifeline as Chelsea transfer tactic slammed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bayern-munich-offer-todd-boehly-major-mason-mount-lifeline-as-chelsea-transfer-tactic-slammed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Lionel Messi Recalls &#8216;Massive Disappointment&#8217; Of PSG Champions League Woes</title>
		<link>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/lionel-messi-recalls-massive-disappointment-of-psg-champions-league-woes/</link>
					<comments>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/lionel-messi-recalls-massive-disappointment-of-psg-champions-league-woes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 11:54:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://fifa.online.mills.edu/?p=100</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Lionel Messi has called his start at former club Paris Saint-Germain &#8220;very tough&#8221;, dubbing two successive failed Champions League bids a &#8220;massive disappointment&#8221;. &#8220;I came to Paris because I liked the club, because I had friends in the dressing room… it seemed easier for me to adapt rather than another destination I could have gone</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/lionel-messi-recalls-massive-disappointment-of-psg-champions-league-woes/">Lionel Messi Recalls &#8216;Massive Disappointment&#8217; Of PSG Champions League Woes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Lionel Messi has called his start at former club Paris Saint-Germain &#8220;very tough&#8221;, dubbing two successive failed Champions League bids a &#8220;massive disappointment&#8221;. &#8220;I came to Paris because I liked the club, because I had friends in the dressing room… it seemed easier for me to adapt rather than another destination I could have gone to,&#8221; Messi told beIN Sports in an interview broadcast Sunday. &#8220;In reality, it was a very tough adaptation, much harder than I expected… with a new game plan, new teammates, a new city.</p>



<p>&#8220;I arrived late, I didn&#8217;t have a pre-season. The start was difficult for me, my family.&#8221;</p>



<p>Messi, 36, signed for PSG in the summer of 2021 after 17 seasons at Barcelona, but will now head Stateside to Inter Miami in the MLS after quitting the French capital.</p>



<p>Messi&#8217;s first season, during which he scored 11 goals in 34 games for PSG, was made harder after he contracted Covid during the winter break back in Argentina, meaning he was sidelined for a month.</p>



<p>&#8220;It took me time to refind my physical form,&#8221; he admitted, adding that the 2022 World Cup in Qatar &#8212; which Messi won with Argentina &#8212; also took its toll.</p>



<p>&#8220;It&#8217;s not an excuse but the World Cup played a big role. Some came back later than others, some were injured, like Neymar.</p>



<p>&#8220;I think, generally, the level of Ligue 1 and the Champions League was affected by the World Cup.&#8221;</p>



<p>Messi admitted that Champions League losses to Real Madrid in 2022 and Bayern Munich this season were a &#8220;massive disappointment&#8221;.</p>



<p>There were even sections of PSG fans who turned on Messi, whistling at him from the stands.</p>



<p>&#8220;In the beginning, it was great, I received a lot of encouragement… but later on a part of the Parisian fanbase treated me differently. The majority treated me well, but there was a rupture with a part of the public,&#8221; he acknowledged.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/lionel-messi-recalls-massive-disappointment-of-psg-champions-league-woes/">Lionel Messi Recalls &#8216;Massive Disappointment&#8217; Of PSG Champions League Woes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/lionel-messi-recalls-massive-disappointment-of-psg-champions-league-woes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bradley Barcola describes playing alongside Alexandre Lacazette as &#8220;an honour&#8221; &#8211; Get French Football News</title>
		<link>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bradley-barcola-describes-playing-alongside-alexandre-lacazette-as-an-honour-get-french-football-news/</link>
					<comments>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bradley-barcola-describes-playing-alongside-alexandre-lacazette-as-an-honour-get-french-football-news/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 11:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://fifa.online.mills.edu/?p=96</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Speaking to L’Équipe, Olympique Lyonnais’ Bradley Barcola (20) has described playing alongside Alexandre Lacazette (32) as “an honour.” Lacazette, who came through the ranks at Lyon, returned to his formative club on a free transfer last summer. In his first season back with Les Gones, the former Arsenal striker scored an impressive 27 goals in</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bradley-barcola-describes-playing-alongside-alexandre-lacazette-as-an-honour-get-french-football-news/">Bradley Barcola describes playing alongside Alexandre Lacazette as &#8220;an honour&#8221; &#8211; Get French Football News</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Speaking to L’Équipe, Olympique Lyonnais’ Bradley Barcola (20) has described playing alongside Alexandre Lacazette (32) as “an honour.”</p>



<p>Lacazette, who came through the ranks at Lyon, returned to his formative club on a free transfer last summer. In his first season back with Les Gones, the former Arsenal striker scored an impressive 27 goals in Ligue 1; only Kylian Mbappé scored more.</p>



<p>In part, Lacazette has Barcola to thank for reaching such a total. The forward, who is currently on France U21 duty, broke into the squad in the second half of the season, making an immediate impact. By the end of the season, Barcola had registered an impressive nine assists and scored five goals.</p>



<p>Barcola has waxed lyrical about his teammate, who during his first spell with OL, was a prolific striker, whilst the former was coming through the club’s academy system. “It’s an honour [to play with him]. When I was young, I admired him. I was in the academy and I was 13 years old and I would never have believed that I’d play alongside him. Just playing with him is mad for me. So winning with him, making him score, it’s exceptional,” said Barcola.</p>



<p>In the interview, Barcola also expressed a desire to remain at the club this summer in order to consolidate his progression and develop further.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bradley-barcola-describes-playing-alongside-alexandre-lacazette-as-an-honour-get-french-football-news/">Bradley Barcola describes playing alongside Alexandre Lacazette as &#8220;an honour&#8221; &#8211; Get French Football News</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/bradley-barcola-describes-playing-alongside-alexandre-lacazette-as-an-honour-get-french-football-news/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Kentucky Pro Football Hall of Fame dinner honored those who reached goals against odds</title>
		<link>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/kentucky-pro-football-hall-of-fame-dinner-honored-those-who-reached-goals-against-odds/</link>
					<comments>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/kentucky-pro-football-hall-of-fame-dinner-honored-those-who-reached-goals-against-odds/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 11:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://fifa.online.mills.edu/?p=93</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Kentucky Pro Football Hall of Fame dinner honored those who reached goals against odds In its two decades, the Kentucky Pro Football Hall of Fame induction dinner has become a fraternity of old friends slapping each other on the back, catching up on family news, sharing memories while welcoming new members. They did all that</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/kentucky-pro-football-hall-of-fame-dinner-honored-those-who-reached-goals-against-odds/">Kentucky Pro Football Hall of Fame dinner honored those who reached goals against odds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Kentucky Pro Football Hall of Fame dinner honored those who reached goals against odds</p>



<p>In its two decades, the Kentucky Pro Football Hall of Fame induction dinner has become a fraternity of old friends slapping each other on the back, catching up on family news, sharing memories while welcoming new members.</p>



<p>They did all that and more Friday night at the Hilton Hotel for the 21st annual ceremony, this year with a bit of a twist.</p>



<p>For the annual Blanton Collier Award, named after the late University of Kentucky and Cleveland Browns football coach, the Blanton Collier Sportsmanship Group chose three Black football coaches who have carved out long and meaningful careers.</p>



<p>Mike Tomlin, Todd Bowles and Lovie Smith couldn’t attend the annual weekend or Friday night’s dinner, but all three sent video messages that made an impact.</p>



<p>Head coach of the Tampa Bay Buccaneers, Bowles spoke of what the honor meant to him given Collier’s reputation for integrity. Tomlin, who has never had a losing season in his 16 years as coach of the Pittsburgh Steelers, talked about the people who had helped him along the way.</p>



<p>Smith, former NFL head coach of the Chicago Bears and Houston Texans, spent a year in Lexington on Bill Curry’s 1992 staff. In his video, Smith displayed a Kentucky football helmet and a game ball from the Cats’ 37-25 win over Indiana in 1992.</p>



<p>During the inductions, Tomlin reappeared on video to tell former Steelers defensive back Mike Mitchell, “I had the pleasure of watching you work.”</p>



<p>Mitchell was one of five inductees in this year’s class, all with their own stories to tell.</p>



<p>Former Washington Redskins offensive line coach Joe Bugel (who played at Western Kentucky) and former Los Angeles Rams defensive lineman Frank Fuller (who played at UK) were inducted posthumously. Fuller died in 1993. Bugel died in 2020.</p>



<p>Inductee Teddy Bridgewater, the former star Louisville quarterback who has played eight years in the NFL, was not at Friday night’s dinner.</p>



<p>Steve Wright, the former Green Bay Packers offensive tackle who played his high school football at Louisville Manual, was in attendance despite recently undergoing back surgery. The 80-year-old Wright played for Bear Bryant at Alabama and Vince Lombardi of the Green Bay Packers.</p>



<p>“There wasn’t a whole lot of difference between the two,” said Wright, who now lives in Augusta, Ga. “They taught you to not only play for your team, but to play for yourself.”</p>



<p>Wright’s likeness — a lineman standing on the sideline with the familiar weather coat hanging from his shoulder pads — was also the model for the Walter Payton Man Award presented each year by the NFL.</p>



<p>Fellow inductee Larry Kirksey also had an Alabama connection. The former Harlan High School and Eastern Kentucky star was the running backs coach on Gene Stallings’ 1992 national title team. Among his previous stops, Kirksey served as an assistant coach on Fran Curci’s 10-1 Kentucky team in 1977.</p>



<p>Kirksey is still coaching. He is on the staff of the USFL’s Birmingham Stallions. And he won a Super Bowl ring in 1994 as wide receivers coach of the San Francisco 49ers.</p>



<p>In fact, star pupil Jerry Rice appeared on video Friday to thank Kirksey for his coaching and congratulate him on his induction. “You are the GOAT,” Rice said. “You’re the champion. I love you.”</p>



<p>Last but not least was Mitchell, who played high school football at both Covington Catholic and Fort Thomas Highlands before starring at Ohio University. Uninvited to the NFL combine, Mitchell was still a second-round draft pick by the Oakland Raiders in 2009. After joining the Steelers in 2013, Mitchell’s star began to shine.</p>



<p>“That was a little awkward,” the 36-year-old Mitchell said after an introduction video that featured many of his hits and celebrations with Pittsburgh. “My girlfriend is here and I don’t think she’s seen that side of me.”</p>



<p>Now an assistant coach with the Indianapolis Colts, Mitchell also talked about achieving a goal against all odds, something that surely hit home with his new fraternity members.</p>



<p>Said Mitchell: “I hope everybody here can experience that feeling of going for something.”</p>



<p>Profile Image of John Clay</p>



<p>John Clay is a sports columnist for the Lexington Herald-Leader. A native of Central Kentucky, he covered UK football from 1987 until being named sports columnist in 2000. He has covered 20 Final Fours and 37 consecutive Kentucky Derbys. Support my work with a digital subscription</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu/kentucky-pro-football-hall-of-fame-dinner-honored-those-who-reached-goals-against-odds/">Kentucky Pro Football Hall of Fame dinner honored those who reached goals against odds</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://fifa.online.mills.edu">FIFA Online Mills</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://fifa.online.mills.edu/kentucky-pro-football-hall-of-fame-dinner-honored-those-who-reached-goals-against-odds/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
